They won't take any shih tzu.
Seven Psychopaths is a comedy, crime film directed by Martin McDonagh.
A struggling screenwriter inadvertently becomes entangled in the Los Angeles criminal
underworld after his oddball friends kidnap a gangster's beloved Shih Tzu.
Marty Faranan, played by Colin Farrell.
Billy Bickle, played by Sam Rockwell.
Charlie Costello, played by Woody Harrelson.
Hans Kieslowski, played by Christopher Walken.
Angela, played by Olga Kurylenko.
Zachariah Rigby, played by Tom Waits.
Seven Psychopaths is a 2012 satirical crime comedy-drama film directed, written, and co-produced by Martin McDonagh and starring Colin Farrell, Sam
Rockwell, Woody Harrelson, and Christopher Walken, with Tom Waits, Abbie Cornish, Olga Kurylenko, and Željko Ivanek in supporting roles.
A co-production between the United Kingdom and the United States, it marks the second
collaboration among McDonagh, Farrell, and Ivanek, following the director's In Bruges (2008).
Seven Psychopaths had its world premiere on 7 September 2012 at the Toronto International Film Festival, and was theatrically
released in the United States and Canada on 12 October 2012, and in the United Kingdom on 5 December 2012.
The film received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of suicide, alcohol, fight, kidnapping, gangster.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.